[Music]
The new TVS Rider, first of all, brother,
we will tell you a little about its features,
later we will take its ownership review from the owner,
what was its showroom price in Patna and what is its on-road price,
which other cars were seen in this segment,
brother, we will discuss all this in this video
and you keep watching the video till the end, first of all,
brother, you get a
digital cluster in it
and here brother, you get a yes port,
from here you can change your mood,
brother, you can upset it, something like this,
brother, you get it in it and its
digital cluster also brother, brother, looks quite attractive, on
this side you get
RPM and here you can
see the time,
here you get the range,
how much has been run, on
this side brother, you get headlight control,
along with your indicator control and
this is your horn, brother, on this side brother,
you get self and in this you get two
drive modes, one and one power mode,
brother, if we talk about the side profile, then the
combination of red and black also looks quite amazing,
in this you get the rear  It only has a single sleeper on the side, the
rest of it looks quite amazing. At the
bottom, you get the TVS
horse symbol of racing, not only that, but it
also gives you a shock
plate, giving you an Apache
look. So, brother, you get the
TVS bedding in the center, and
in this you get DRL in dual zone,
in triple zone you get the headline in LED base,
and from the front,
you get a look like this
[Music]
brother, here you get the stop,
here you get the numbering light, you get this
reflector, and this
reflector brother, you get this side as well,
and on this side also you get a
small indicator like this,
which enhances the look from the rear as well,
like you get it,
and in this you get a disc brake in the front,
and you do
n't get a normal drum brake at the rear, and now let's talk to
its owner Avinash ji, first of all,
congratulations to you for
this price range in the segment for new bike riders.  I had
seen which vehicles are available in the market,
I saw the price was very high and low
but I saw the car's participation in this segment, okay, first of all I
saw the complete Gunda SP Pulsar
125 Glamour, I saw this bike and
after seeing it I purchased it, I
selected the rider from it, its look is
very beautiful to see,
I found this bike to be the most comfortable, that's why
I used this bike, its
features are also very good, in comparison to other bikes,
so
what is its on road price in Patna, Bihar, its price was
₹16300 for me,
you got ₹16000 on road price, so are
you spending that much money, look at TVS, you are
satisfied till now,
quite satisfied, its mileage is also very good and it is also very comfortable to
ride and the
shocks here are also very good,
as you told,
you are driving it for two-three days, so in two-three
days you have come to know many things like
what negative thing are you facing in it and
what is your biggest positive thing,
it dips at the back and it is a little dr  It gets a
little dull, you must have felt a positive thing in it too,
after driving for two-three days
it has given double the mood, okay, there is
no one in this and one more thing is in this, it is
found here,
in case of emergency you can charge it with your mobile,
like if you drove for two-three days then you
must have done night drive also once, so
how is its lighting, its lighting is quite
good, as in this segment four-five
bikes have come in 125 cc bike, but in this there is
a Honda SP in which LED light is
available, the rest of the time it is halogen, this has LED
light, three lights are available in ours,
here all three of them
glow together, so quite good light and these have
negative positive, it has been 2 days, I
cannot tell much, now after like 4 months, 5
minutes, 6 months you will take its review, then
I will be able to tell very well what is negative, what is positive,
come on, thank you very much for giving your precious time,
thanks, how did you like the car, how did you like the
video, how did you like the ownership review, please do
tell in the comments and thank
you all brothers for watching the video  Thank you very much
Thanks for watching